David Provost

I am a CEGEP programming graduate with 2 years of IT experience looking for my next position in the information technologies field. I am motivated and excited to be the next addition to your team. Whatever I don't know yet I am happy to learn.

EXPERIENCE

Mckesson Automation, Montreal — Bilingual Technical Service Analyst

SEPTEMBER 2021 - JULY 2023

Receive calls, voicemails and emails related to new or existing cases using Five 9 and Cisco IP phone.

Create and manage cases in Salesforce, keep detailed logs of customer interactions and troubleshooting steps.

Supply detailed instructions to fix hardware and software issues. Offer training for those products.

Access user documentation and available knowledge on the company's products to offer support and gather knowledge from the senior support staff for more complex issues.

Connect to customers with Tight VNC, TeamViewer and RTSS Gateways. Install hardware and configure software on site along with other technicians. Mostly using Microsoft Teams.

Managing server databases with SQL Server Management Studio. Using SQL Daily.

Emili Gestionnaire Animalier, Laval — *Intern*

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

Programming of functionalities and pages for a web app using Laravel PHP framework and bootstrap.

Archiving of this project using Git and local Server applications (VScode, SourceTree, Laragon).

EDUCATION

Montmorency CEGEP, Laval — DEC Computer Science - Programming

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2021

Java, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS, Git. Creation of multiple mock-up Object-Oriented applications in Java, PHP, Multiple PHP frameworks, Git (With and without a GUI). Overview of Angular, C++ and C#.

Installation, Imaging, configuration and troubleshooting of Windows 7/10 and Linux (Fedora, Ubuntu)

6102 Rue des Sizerins Laval, Quebec, Canada H7L 5V2 (514) 892-1398 dvdp26@gmail.com

SKILLS

Object Oriented Programming

Java, C# and C++

PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

Laravel, Laragon, CakePHP

SQL, SQL server management studio

JUnit, and the usage of programming Quality Assurance

Windows 7, 8, 10, Windows server.

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc.)

Microsoft Teams, Outlook

Tight VNC, TeamViewer

Windows Imaging/Installation

VMWare, VirtualBox

Customer support/Soft Skills

Art/Photo editing software, Clip studio Paint, Sai.

Unity Game Engine

LANGUAGES

Fully fluent in both French and English. Written, spoken and read.